While Rio’s eyes widened, he still managed to speak in a calm tone. “...May I ask the reason why?”

“T-That’s... because...” Flora’s voice trembled slightly as she looked up at Rio’s face right before her.

There’s no mistaking the fact she remembers me. What do I do? Rio calmly tried to think of a way to deal with the situation as he looked down at Flora.

When it came to Flora hearing his conversation with Lucius, he had no regrets. He considered the conversation a necessary ritual to precede their battle, after all.

However, Flora’s memory of him was clearer than he thought it’d be, and her strong feelings about it were a little beyond his expectations. He had no idea what she was thinking. After all, he’d had no interactions with her at the academy, and their social statuses were far from each other.

If she’s this desperate about it, it may be impossible to fully deny everything, Rio sensed, which left him with limited options. He could admit to the truth honestly, come up with some kind of convincing excuse, or purposefully confuse her to change the subject...

At any rate, the decision came down to the fact that Rio didn’t trust Flora. While he believed she wasn’t a bad person, he would be in a bind if his admission caused her to act rashly in response. That was why he had to make the truth as vague as possible.

Which meant the safest option would be...

“I... I always wanted to apologize! I always wanted to say thank you!” Flora proclaimed with every fiber of her being.

She had always felt regret for her own failure in being unable to do anything during Rio’s former academy days, when he was being discriminated against right before her very eyes. That was why she couldn’t simply forget the existence of the person who had saved her. She had made a vow that she wouldn’t forget. The sudden encounter had left her head blank as a sheet, but whether it was coincidence or fate, she couldn’t let this once in a lifetime chance of reuniting with Rio slip past her fingers.

“Whatever for?” Rio merely tried to divert the truth with a troubled look.

“For what happened at the academy!” Flora said, getting to the core of the matter.

After a long moment of hesitation, Rio responded. “...I cannot think of any reason why I should be receiving such words of gratitude and apology from you. If you are referring to this incident, then please do not let it bother you. There was simply some business to attend to between me and that man.”

Even Flora could read what he was implying with that, body shaking as she asked, “...Am I being a bother?”

Rio took the clinging Flora by the shoulders and moved her back a distance so that he could speak to her while bowing his head. “Of course not. But right now, I am Haruto. If your Highness insists on feeling gratitude and apology for this incident, I would request that you kindly forget the name Rio. That would be more than enough.”

“Ah, uh...” That seemed to shock Flora, as her expression was lost for a moment. She tried to say something, but her mouth didn’t move.

There was a person resembling Rio before her, and the final words coming from him resonated strangely within her head. As her head rapidly cooled down, an indescribable feeling swirled violently in her chest.

Perhaps this was a punishment for her own foolishness. After how much misery he had been put through by her and the others around her, it was simply too convenient to be given a chance to apologize like this. Once she came to that conclusion, Flora suddenly felt extremely ashamed.

I... really am a fool... Flora thought bitterly. She felt so sorry and helpless with impatience, as she had been desperately searching for something she could do. Soon, she realized there was only one thing she could do.

“Of... course. I-I’m sorry. I was... mistaken, and asked something strange... I’m sorry. I’m so sorry,” Flora cried big drops of tears as she bowed her head with a heavily trembling voice.

“No, there’s no need to cry in apology...” Rio felt rather helpless, but this was for the best. There was no other choice right now, he told himself.

“I’m sorry. I’m sorry...” Flora continued to apologize with her head down. She rubbed her eyes, desperately holding back the tears, then bit down hard on her lip and stifled her emotions.

After a moment, Flora slowly raised her head. There were no longer any tears flowing, but it was clear that she had been crying. She had an awful look on her face.

“I’ll escort you back to the city.” Rio averted his eyes awkwardly.

“...Yes, please.” Flora nodded weakly.

“Yes, somehow,” Rio nodded with a strained smile.

“So I heard on the way here.” Aria had already learned this on the way, so she wasn’t particularly surprised. Instead, she watched Rio’s side profile.

“Leave the idle chit-chat here and quickly show Sir Haruto to our master,” she ordered Cosette and Natalie.

“As you wish,” the two of them agreed respectfully.

◇　◇　◇

The attendants led Rio to an area with several pavilions set up; a field hospital where the wounded were carried. Inside one of the tents, Liselotte and several of her attendants were using Cura to heal the wounded as assistants circled around them in feverish haste.

“Sir Haruto. Aria.” Liselotte was in the middle of healing a severely wounded soldier with a serious face, but she immediately noticed Rio and called out to them.

“Please pay me no mind and continue your treatment,” Rio urged.

“Much obliged. But I’m almost done anyway, so please wait there for a moment. ...Okay, all done.” Liselotte confirmed that the wound on the soldier’s abdomen was completely closed before deactivating her healing magic.

“T-Thank you very much, Lady Liselotte! O-Oww?!” The soldier immediately tried to spring up to thank Liselotte. However, he was soon reminded of the pain in his stomach and grimaced.

“Didn’t I just tell you that the wound may still open, so make sure you avoid rigorous movement for a few days? Don’t even think about using your stomach muscles. It was a pretty deep wound, you know,” Liselotte said with a sigh.

“I-I have no excuse.” The soldier hung his head in shame.

“Okay. If you feel anything weird, call one of the attendants nearby immediately. Now, take care of yourself,” Liselotte said, standing up with a grin. The soldier that received treatment was completely distracted, watching Liselotte’s retreating back with a sloppy expression. Meanwhile, the other wounded men were glaring at that soldier in jealousy.

Liselotte ignored the conversations going on behind her. “Sorry for the wait, Sir Haruto. Lady Cecilia and Lady Aishia are assisting the healing efforts in the tent next to us. Let’s move there first.”

“Are you sure you can leave?” Rio looked around the room.

“Yes. The rest will be left to the three over there. And you’re back too, Aria,” Liselotte beamed, looking over at Aria, Natalie, and Cosette.

“Yes. I just arrived with Sir Haruto,” Aria replied.

“With Sir Haruto?” Liselotte tilted her head.

“We ran into each other by coincidence,” Rio explained.

“I dropped by the northwest area after cleaning up the monsters at the west gate,” Aria added.

“I see. Do you have anything urgent to report on your side?”

Aria shook her head quietly. “...Nothing that can’t wait until later. I shall report the details to you at a later time.”

“Okay, sounds good. Then, Sir Haruto — please come this way.”

“Understood.” Rio followed Liselotte out of the tent.

“By the way, Sir Haruto. Did you find any hints about the kidnapper?” Liselotte asked, stopping outside of the tent.

“No. He should have suffered fairly fatal wounds, and yet I didn’t even see any stains of blood.” Rio shook his head in disappointment.

“Is that so... At any rate, I would like to organize all the information first. Extermination of the monsters at the east and west gate is pretty much completed, and the situation has settled a bit, but we cannot relax yet. I’m sorry to ask this, but could you tell me more at a later time with Princess Flora and Duke Huguenot in attendance?” Liselotte asked with an apologetic face.

“Of course — I have no objections,” Rio said readily.

“Thank you very much. Fortunately, the attendants dispatched to every area of the city have started to return, so the mansion won’t be lacking personnel any longer. There’s no need for you and your friends to trouble yourselves anymore. I will arrange for a room where you can rest immediately.” There was no way Rio and his companions could return to their room at the inn in this situation.

Rio decided to obediently accept Liselotte’s offer. “...I understand. I will gladly take you up on that.”

Instead, Liselotte looked at Duke Huguenot and proceeded with the discussion. “That still isn’t certain yet. I’m also interested in this man called Reiss that Sir Haruto and Princess Flora mentioned...”

“I’ve also heard of the name Reiss before. It’s the name of the Proxia Empire diplomat who was secretly communicating with the house of Duke Arbor. Or course, it may just be two people with the same name...” Duke Huguenot murmured, and Liselotte turned to address Rio.

“Princess Flora said that his face was hidden by a hood, but were you able to catch a glimpse of his appearance at all, Sir Haruto...?”

“No, I couldn’t see anything either. Even if I had seen the face of that Proxia Empire diplomat, there’s no guarantee they are the same person,” Rio shook his head apologetically. He could make a presumption based on stature and voice, but there wasn’t enough decisive evidence to prove it.

“Which means it would be more reliable to pursue Lucius’ tracks, whose background we understand,” Liselotte suggested.

Duke Huguenot seemed to have no objections. “I will gather my forces and investigate to see whether anyone among them has had any points of connection with him in the past or present. It will require a trip back to Rodania, though.”

“Thank you for your efforts. I will put an inquiry in at the adventurer’s guild just in case, but if he has suspended his mercenary activities, I don’t believe there will be much chance of success.” Liselotte bowed her head deeply in request.

Various discussions continued after that, and another hour passed before they dispersed.

◇　◇　◇

The next morning, Rio was once again summoned by Liselotte. Instead of the meeting room from last night, he was led into a drawing room.

“Thank you for coming, Sir Haruto. Please, have a seat,” Liselotte welcomed Rio brightly. Present in the room was the head attendant Aria, Duke Huguenot, and Flora. There was no sign of Hiroaki or Roanna.

“Excuse me. What is everyone gathered here for, if I may ask?” Rio asked, then sat down on a loveseat. They should have concluded all discussions about the monster attack and Lucius last night.

“If it isn’t too much of a bother to you, we wanted to ask what your plans are for the future, and also discuss various things relating to your reward.” Liselotte sat on the single-seater sofa opposite to Rio and stated their business. Flora was seated on the sofa next to her, while the one beside that sat Duke Huguenot.

“I’ve actually had some urgent matter suddenly come up, so I was thinking of leaving Amande within the next few days,” Rio informed.

“Urgent matter, you say?”

“Yes. I plan on heading to the Galarc Kingdom capital, Galtuuk, first.”

“...Is that so? In that case, we must prepare our tokens of gratitude for you with even more haste.” Liselotte had wanted Rio to remain in Amande so that they could deepen their relationship, but she couldn’t make demands in this situation.

“I’m sure your hands must be full with the aftermath of the monster attack on Amande, Lady Liselotte. There’s no need for you to push yourself.” Rio shook his head gently.

“I cannot allow things to settle like that — We are only here now because of your efforts. Rewarding you should be my highest priority,” Liselotte said.

“Is there anything you desire? To be honest, your merits have been so great, we’ve been having a little trouble determining how to reward you. Of course, Liselotte and I fully intend on rewarding you separately. Whether it is status or money, we will gladly prepare whatever is within our abilities for you. If you have any requests, I’d like to hear them,” Duke Huguenot said smoothly.

“...” Flora stared at Rio’s face fixedly.

“I... see.” Rio contemplated for a moment, before speaking up. “In that case, there is one thing I would like to request of Lady Liselotte.”

“Yes?” Liselotte returned Rio’s gaze directly.

“If it is possible, could you allow me to participate in the banquet where the heroes are to be introduced?”

“The banquet where the heroes are to be introduced... The banquet being held at our kingdom’s royal castle. Is that correct? And you want to attend yourself, Sir Haruto?” Taken aback by the unexpected request, Liselotte looked at Rio carefully as she confirmed what he’d said.

“Yes. I wish to meet Lady Satsuki Sumeragi.” Rio nodded, stating his objective shortly.

“...May I ask why?”

“I’m sorry. I know that this is impudent of me, and for that I am most ashamed, but could I ask that you refrain from asking my reason as part of my reward? Of course, I have absolutely no intention of harming the hero in any way, and will explain the situation properly when the right time comes,” Rio said, bowing his head deeply to Liselotte.

Liselotte paused for a long moment before resolving herself and accepting. “...I understand. It should be possible for you to accompany me when I go.”

If a person of unclear background was taken to the banquet hosted by the king and queen themselves and caused an issue, everything would fall on Liselotte’s head, which was why requests like Rio’s would normally be out of the question. However, her debt to Rio was equivalently as large as his request was outrageous.

“Thank you very much.” Rio bowed his head deeply to Liselotte once more.

Liselotte shook her head with a cheerful smile. “Not at all. I will eagerly await the time when we can talk more about this.”

Duke Huguenot, who had been watching the exchange between Rio and Liselotte silently, finally spoke up. “...Hmm, it seems like the reward from Liselotte has been decided. Now, may I hear what you request from us?”

Flora seemed nervous, as her expression was rather stiff as she stared at Rio.

Rio looked between Duke Huguenot and Flora. “...To be honest, I cannot think of anything at the moment.”

“Hmm. So you’d like hold onto the request for later. Is that correct?” Duke Huguenot asked, confirming the gist of Rio’s statement.

“Yes. I would be grateful if you could lend me your assistance if I were to need it in the future.”

“...Understood,” Duke Huguenot nodded with a wry smile, surprised at how indifferent he seemed. Meanwhile, Flora seemed to have an opinion about that, as she was watching Rio with a vexed expression.

“My reward is also lacking with just an invitation to the banquet. When you need assistance, please rely on what power I have too,” Liselotte offered immediately.

“I would appreciate that greatly.” Rio smiled warmly.

◇　◇　◇

Two days later...

It was morning when Rio departed from Amande with Aishia and Celia. At present, they were standing outside the mansion entrance and being sent off. The ones seeing them off were Liselotte, Flora, and Duke Huguenot, along with Hiroaki and Roanna. Furthermore, Aria, Natalie, Cosette, Chloe, and all the attendant ladies of the estate had lined up.

“Thank you all for everything. To be sent off by so many people is an honor.” Rio bowed once, facing Liselotte and the rest. Behind him, Aishia and Celia, who had their faces hidden by their hoods, bowed similarly.

Liselotte gave her cheerful words of parting on behalf of everyone present. “We should be the ones thanking you. We shall look forward to seeing you again in a month and a half, on the date that we agreed on.”

“Yes, thank you very much,” Rio replied with a smile.

“I would love to talk to you two some more as well, if that is to your liking!” Liselotte said while looking at Aishia and Celia.

In the end, Aishia and Celia had been shut away in their rooms the entire time so that most of the people in the mansion, including Liselotte, never interacted with them during their stay. There was the fact that Rio hadn’t tried to put the two of them in the spotlight, but with Aishia having close combat abilities on par with Rio and Cecilia being such a remarkable sorcerer, Liselotte’s curiosity was piqued. At the very least, she thought she could venture with a little greed and ask for another opportunity to make contact with them.

“Yes. If the opportunity arises, then gladly.” Celia nodded amiably with a charming smile. Aishia was silent, but nodded too.

“...” Most of the men and women standing on Liselotte’s side found their gazes captivated. After all, from what they could see, both Aishia and Celia had beauty that couldn’t normally be seen on an everyday basis. Liselotte and her attendants were also a gathering of beautiful girls, but most of them accepted the fact that they came in second in terms of appearances. The only attendant on par would probably be Aria. Otherwise, there was Flora and Liselotte, followed by Roanna as runner-up. Hiroaki’s mouth was open as he stared at Aishia and Celia in a daze.

...Huh, she looks familiar for some reason? Aria tilted her head in suspicion, watching Celia’s face. Celia seemed to notice her gaze, and her expression grew a bit awkward.

When Rio realized that too, he urged for their departure. “We will be going now, then.”

“Yes, please take care. Thank you for everything you have done,” Liselotte said, clutching her skirt gracefully and bowing her head. The attendants behind her all lowered their heads, seeing Rio and the others off.

Unsure of how to respond, Miharu looked to Rio for confirmation. If Rio gave the wrong order here, he would be revealing that he could understand Japanese to Liselotte, but they had thankfully established a sign in advance just for this situation.

What should I do? Join the conversation too? But... Rio decided to observe for now, placing his right hand over his left hand and tapping his index finger twice. In other words: a yes.

“Ah, umm... Yes,” Miharu answered hesitantly in Japanese.

“Are you wondering why I can speak Japanese? Or did you expect that I would be able to speak Japanese?” Liselotte giggled, guessing at what Miharu could be thinking at the moment.

“Umm, why did you suddenly speak in Japanese?” Miharu asked. While the right answer was actually the latter, she was more curious as to the reason why Liselotte suddenly spoke in Japanese.

“It’s because you were able to speak the language of this world clearly. Your pronunciation wasn’t entirely fluent, but the movement of your lips matches the sounds, so I deduced that you were able to understand the language of this world. That is the reason,” Liselotte replied.

“What do you mean by that?” Miharu didn’t seem to understand with just that explanation. She tilted her head dubiously.

I see... Rio grasped the reason with just that information and was very impressed, though he didn’t show it on his face.

“The only hero I’ve met so far has been Sakata, but he’s just been speaking in Japanese. It seems to be automatically translated into the language of our world through some ability. I believe this is one of the powers of the divine arms, but it also means that if you look closely, you’ll see his lips don’t match his words.”

“Umm...” Miharu still didn’t look convinced.

“In other words, he didn’t realize that the products of the Ricca Guild were named after Japanese or Earth words. But you knew, didn’t you?” Liselotte tilted her head and confirmed.

“Ah, yes,” Miharu said honestly. She had discussed this with Rio in advance; they decided it was okay to answer honestly in this regard.

“In that case, you must have anticipated that the item must have been invented by either me or someone from the Ricca Guild, no? In fact, that’s why you’re here, is it not?”

“Y-Yes.”

“That’s why I spoke in Japanese from the start, rather than hide in a roundabout way. The reason I chose to use Earth words for the Ricca Guild’s products was to search for those who were like me, as a message. I didn’t intend on hiding myself from those who received my message.”

“That’s... amazing.” Overwhelmed by Liselotte’s sharp intellect, Miharu murmured her awe quietly. It was all she could do to keep up with her words, leaving her no room to think.

“Thank you for the praise. But there’s one thing I’m curious about,” said Liselotte.

“W-What is it?” Miharu asked fearfully.

“Japanese shouldn’t exist in this world. So, how did you learn the language of this country? It seems like you’ve already acquired the language to an easily conversational level, but reaching that with self-study would require a tremendous amount of time. At the very least, it would be impossible to achieve in the time since the hero was summoned.”

“...” Miharu listened to Liselotte’s careful words with an uncomfortable expression.

“In other words, you would have needed an excellent teacher. Now who could have played that role... With all due respect, Sir Haruto, could it have been you?” Liselotte suddenly looked at Rio and asked in Japanese.

“Ah, no...” Miharu’s expression stiffened as she looked to Rio in a fluster. Meanwhile, Rio’s expression hadn’t even flinched. He had prepared an excuse in advance, after all.

“Yes, it is exactly as you suspect. Your observation skills and deductive abilities are most commendable,” Rio praised Liselotte and easily confirmed her conjecture. This time, Liselotte’s expression stiffened.

“Then... really... Were you — were you reincarnated too? Did you regain your memories of Earth as you were living in this world? Your name — Haruto — is it...” In a rare display of impatience, Liselotte tensed up and asked one question after another, but Rio put a stop to that.

“Please wait a moment. We have come here today for a different matter. I’m sure you must be limited on time too, so could we wrap up that business first?” Rio said, choosing to use the language of this world.

“...Please excuse my behavior, I got too excited,” Liselotte apologized, returning to her senses.

“No, it’s just that that discussion will take some time to get through, so we should plan another day where we can chat without interruption. For now, let’s leave this discussion at my confirmation that I have memories of my past life as a Japanese person. Can we keep this a secret between us? I have no intention of revealing this to others that I do not know well.” Rio shook his head respectfully, confirming the bare minimum. Of course he was willing to expand on this discussion later, but he didn’t want to lose sight of their original objective here.

“Yes. At present, the hero, Sakata Hiroaki isn’t aware of this either, so I would be grateful if we could keep it that way. I don’t plan on telling anyone other than those that noticed my hint, so I can promise that I will not reveal your secret,” Liselotte agreed with a wry smile.

“Thank you very much. I shall promise the same.” Rio bowed respectfully.

“Then will you tell me more about this other matter? It seems I’ve made the mood a little strange...” Liselotte said, smiling faintly. As a result of what she’d started, this space was now occupied by one world hopper and two reincarnations. There was a sense of something hard to describe — almost like familiarity.

“It’s about Miharu. I wish to request that she joins us at the banquet where Satsuki will be introduced,” Rio said with a faint smile of his own.

“Sure, I don’t mind,” Liselotte agreed readily.

“...Is it really okay?” Rio’s eyes widened in surprise. He’d expected there to be more resistance and discussion surrounding the topic.

“Yes. Miharu herself wants to attend the banquet, right? I do owe a great debt to Sir Haruto. That much of a request is easy to fill. Now that I know your goal, I have ascertained that you have no ulterior motives. It won’t make a difference if Miharu joins as well. More importantly, I wish to return to the discussion of our past lives as soon as possible,” Liselotte said, giggling with a smile true to herself.

“...Umm, thank you very much, Lady Liselotte.” Miharu had been observing part of the conversation in a daze, but she suddenly thanked Liselotte.

“No, don’t mention it. It was thanks to you that I was able to meet someone in the same situation as me.” Liselotte shook her head slowly, looking intently at Rio.

“...By which you mean someone who has memories of their past life, right?” Rio guessed.

“Yes. I’ve always wondered why I was reborn into this world, and whether there were other people who were reborn just like me. As I said earlier, that was the reason why I used Earth words in the Ricca Guild’s products.”

“What made you think that?”

“I had a hunch. Based on the situation of my death, there should have been other people who died too. And if I had been reborn, then it was possible that the same happened to those people. That was my thinking.”

“...I see.” Rio stared at Liselotte. He had always held the same suspicion as well. He had managed to meet Latifa, after all.

“In that case, it’s possible that I knew of you.” With a serious expression, Liselotte gulped, then took a deep breath. “Sir Haruto... Did you perhaps pass away in a traffic accident in your past life?”

“...Before I answer that question... Miharu.” Rio did not respond to the question right away, instead addressing Miharu beside him.

“Y-Yes?” Miharu had been listening intently, flinching when she replied.

“Could I ask you to step outside for a moment?” Rio asked Miharu.

“Huh? Ah, but...” Miharu hesitated, wanting to remain present. However —

“...Please,” Rio bowed his head deeply.

“Uh, ah... I-I understand,” Miharu said dejectedly, her voice fading away. She couldn’t say no; Rio’s gaze asked her not to overstep herself.

“The attendants outside will lead you to another room. Please, follow me,” Liselotte couldn’t help but interrupt, urging Miharu out as well.

“...Okay.” In low spirits, Miharu reluctantly moved to leave the room. She slowly opened the door with a clack to see Aria and Natalie waiting outside.

“It seems Miharu isn’t feeling too well. Please lead her to another room to rest,” Liselotte ordered the two attendants.

The two attendants exchanged a look before Natalie stepped forward to lead her. “Understood. Lady Miharu, please come this way.” Aria continued to guard the door from outside intruders.

“...I apologize for that,” Rio said once the door was shut again. “It seemed like we were veering into territory I had yet to reveal to Miharu, so I wasn’t entirely prepared for it.” He bowed his head deeply.

“No, I should be the one to apologize. I brought it up out of the blue...” Liselotte apologized regretfully.

“No, let’s continue the conversation. Your question was whether I had died in a traffic accident... The answer is yes — that is exactly right,” Rio said with a strained smile, his face slightly unhappy.

“I knew it... Who... Who were you in your past life? Were you the young man in university? Or the little girl in primary school? The bus driver?” It was as though years of Liselotte’s questions had been defrosted all at once, filling her with a sense of triumph and impatience as she fearfully asked question after question.

“...I was the university student. And you?”

“The high school student. Do you... remember me?”

“I do recall that you were there, I believe...” Rio said, looking back on his vague memories.

“We’ve never had any direct contact. But I do remember you,” Liselotte said, examining Rio’s face with a smile.

“Is that so?”

“Yes. You always looked sad, so I was a little curious about you. And...” Liselotte looked at Rio’s face, pausing with meaning.

“...And?” Rio tilted his head curiously.

“No... But you also helped out the elementary school girl that time she missed her stop and cried on the bus, right?” Liselotte shook her head slowly, recalling her memories with fondness.

“You even remember that...”

“Yes. By the way, in my past life I was Rikka — Minamoto Rikka. The Ricca Guild’s name actually derives from my own name in my past life,” Liselotte revealed, now in a nostalgic mood.

“Rikka, is it? I... My name was Haruto. Amakawa Haruto.” With the flow of the conversation as it was, Rio had no choice but to reveal his name.

“I figured. It’s a name you hear here too, but I always thought it sounded more Japanese.” Liselotte smiled happily, her eyes thin lines.

“Lady Liselotte... No, Rikka. I have a favor to ask of you,” Rio began with a serious look.

“...Yes?” Liselotte adjusted her posture and replied.

“I’d like you to keep all information surrounding this a secret from Miharu, including my name.”

“...May I inquire as to why?” Liselotte asked, staring at Rio.

“Miharu was summoned to this world from Earth, four years before we died.”

“Huh...?” Liselotte’s eyes widened.

“The same probably applies to the other heroes. Timeline-wise, we died after they were summoned to this world, yet we were reincarnated before they arrived. It is something we will have to tell them someday, but I want you to keep this from Miharu and the heroes for now,” Rio explained awkwardly.

“I... see...” Even Liselotte was stunned by that bombshell, but she somehow managed to utter a response.

“If we talk about our previous lives, Miharu will definitely notice the gap in timelines. That’s why I’d like you to entrust the timing of when to tell her to me,” Rio said, staring at Liselotte’s contemplative face.

“I understand, if that’s the case... But shouldn’t it be fine to tell her your previous name, at least?” Liselotte asked curiously. She didn’t understand why he had specifically requested that.

“...I cannot. Because Miharu should know who I was in my previous life.” With a dark expression, Rio shook his head.

“...” Liselotte was shocked once again.

“I revealed all of this to you because I trust you. Would you please consider doing this favor for me?” Rio bowed his head once again.

Liselotte took a breath to calm herself. “Please raise your head. I promise to do just that... But if possible, could you tell me a little more about you and your past life? And Miharu too, of course.”

“...Sure. If there’s anything I can discuss, I would love to. There are some things that I can’t discuss, but I shouldn’t keep Miharu waiting any longer for now. Could we set another date where we can sit down and talk casually?” Rio exhaled in relief, slumping his posture and nodding. He couldn’t get a clear read on Liselotte’s intentions yet, so he would keep Aki and Masato hidden for now.

“Of course.” Liselotte also nodded happily. There were many things about Rio that she was curious about, and they weren’t only to do with their past life. Even if it couldn’t be everything, simply receiving an agreement to learn more made her very happy.

“Then how about we wrap up today with one last question? If there’s anything you’re particularly curious about, I shall answer as much as I can to the best of my abilities,” Rio offered.

“I understand. Then, as it relates to the banquet, may I ask something with regards to Miharu? As well as what you’re thinking of doing in the future, after meeting Lady Satsuki. Or, it could be possible to meet Lady Satsuki before the banquet, in order to talk.” While she actually wanted to ask more about Rio, she didn’t want to be rude right off the bat.

“Really?” Rio’s eyes widened slightly in wonder.

“Yes. Presently, all requests to meet Lady Satsuki have been denied, whether from internal or external of the kingdom. But if it were her friend, there may possibly be a chance. However, I’ll be going to the capital right before the banquet, so the request to meet her would have to be made then.”

“I would be very grateful for that. However, it’s not something I can decide alone, so would it be possible for me to bring that information back and consider it more?”

“Of course. There’s still plenty of time until the banquet. As long as you give me a reply before then, it won’t be a problem,” Liselotte said warmly.

“Thank you very much,” Rio said and bowed his head. After that, Rio gave Liselotte a simple explanation of Miharu’s intentions and they wrapped up their talk, agreeing to meet again in ten days before Rio went to find Miharu.

“Sorry for the wait, Miharu,” Rio said once he was led to the separate room where Miharu was waiting. Miharu was staring at the tea set left on the table before her in a daze, a picture of true boredom. She quickly stood up when Rio appeared.

“Ah, are you done already?”

“...Yes. I’ll explain on the way back. Shall we go?” Rio asked. He implied his need to meet up with Aishia and Celia by going home like this for today.

“See you again in ten days. Thank you for today.” Liselotte didn’t stop them, seeing the two off. Thus, Rio and Miharu were led out the mansion.

◇　◇　◇

On the way back from the mansion...

“It may be possible for you to see Satsuki before the banquet,” Rio informed Miharu.

“...Really?” Miharu asked in wonder.

“Yes. Telling Liselotte about my past life was a bit unforeseen, but thanks to that, we were able to drop our pretenses and speak honestly with each other. She said that she’d try to put together a meeting before the banquet for us, if you so wish,” Rio explained to Miharu as brightly as possible.

“...Thank you very much. You’ve made things more and more beneficial for us. I honestly don’t know how to thank you...” In contrast, Miharu frowned apologetically.

“Don’t worry about it,” Rio said with a faint smile.

“It’s impossible,” Miharu muttered quietly.

“Huh...?” Rio was taken aback, his eyes widening a bit. Miharu stopped in her steps and grabbed onto Rio’s sleeves.

“I can’t do it anymore. It just won’t leave my mind. Haruto... Why do you... Why are you willing to go so far for us?” Miharu asked Rio clingingly.

Rio thought for a moment. “...Because I couldn’t just pretend to turn a blind eye. And I’ve already started helping, so I want to see it through to the end.”

“Is that all, though?” Miharu asked dubiously.

“What do you mean by that...?”

“I also... I also...” A conflicted but contemplative look appeared on Miharu’s face. I also want to hear about your past life, please... Those words were right on the tip of her tongue, but she just couldn’t get them out.

She knew the reason why... But she was too scared to know for sure. What if she was wrong? With Rio actually before her, that possibility ran through her head, making her too scared to ask.

“What is it?” Rio looked at Miharu’s face as though he was being pulled in.

Hey, people around you are staring. Aishia’s telepathic voice suddenly echoed in the back of their heads after being silent the entire time.

“Uh...” Miharu flinched. She had completely forgotten Aishia had been there the whole time, being that she was so silent. They were currently in the noble district, but like Aishia said, people’s gazes were turned towards them curiously.

“Yeah, let’s go back. Miharu, we can continue this once we’re back at home. We should hurry and tell Aki and Masato about today’s news, too,” Rio said.

“...Okay,” Miharu said in frustration.

After that, the two of them left Amande and entered the forest off the main road, before floating into the air and heading for the stone house. But in the end, Miharu was unable to continue their conversation.